SANKET SANJAY KAMBLE

Currently, a **UX Designer**, working with the healthcare industry in Bangalore, India. It's been 3 years within UX and a year within development professionally, added 2 years of experience academically. I am practising user-centred design and aligning products as a solution to the business requirement.



https://sanketkamblein.github.io/sanketux/







WORK EXPERIENCE



May 2020 - present

UX Designer

US Tech Solutions (Cerner on contract) Bangalore

Working in the vertical 'order and clinical management' and solving issues of 50+ client members for their 100 million patients. My responsibilities are:

- Validations of the screens for the accessibility issues
- Gathering requirements through the clients from the global market (US, Europe) and following Cerner's user-centred design process to create solution and UI



June 2019 - Jan 2020

Associate UX Designer - Axon

Informatica Bangalore

Quality Assurance issues in the UI for the Data governance tool called Axon.



Nov 2018 - June 2019

UX & UI Designer - Smartech

Netcore Solutions pvt Imtd Mumbai

- Solved the issues of digital marketeers by giving a solution that impacted 5000+ Enterprise customers.
- Conducted the 'design sprint' to redesign of the 'email campaign' module of 'Smartech'. I was responsible for user research, customer journey mapping, Information Architecture, wire-frames, user testing and the design
- Reorganized the **UI of 'Web-messages'** using netcore's design system.
- Successfully deployed 90+ templates for web-messages.



June 2017 - July 2017

IISc - SID Bangalore

 UX/UI Design Intern - Android | IOS Application **Ergoproxemics**

User Research, Concept Generation

UX Design Intern - Mimyk M2D2 lab

Information Architecture, LoFi Mockups



July 2015 - July 2016

Associate Software Developer (SAP ABAP) Accenture services private limited Mumbai



EDUCATION



July 2016 - June 2018

Master of Design at Centre for Product Design and Manufacturing, Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore



August 2011 - June 2015

Bachelor of Engineering (Computer Engineering) at Sardar Patel Institute of Technology, University of Mumbai



ACHIEVEMENT

August 2020

Winning team (covicloud) MIT covid 19 challenge

In a 48 hours of hackathon teamed with strangers, where pitched a solution as co.weCloud



PROJECTS

2020-21

co.WeCloud

Designed a solution that provides consolidated information and bridges the gap between patient and medical facility.

2017-18

Smart solution for monitoring workers' health and vitals

Designed and Developed an IOT wearable as a major thesis and it is added portfolio for IISc -Industry 4.0

2017

Biomediclal Solution for Urinary Incontinence



PUBLICATION

2019 - ICCIDS 2019

Design and development of an assistive device for the visually impaired Procedia Computer Science Journal, Elsevier